### THOMAS MOSKAL

#### Auburn, NY. 13021 MoskalTM@gmail.com • 315-877-6614

Experienced team coordinator, excelling in diverse, fast-paced environments. Confident interpersonal communication. Avid interest in current developments in the fields of Computer Science, IoT, virtual/augmented reality. Dedicated, ethical and motivated. Committed to outstanding customer service and service management.

### **CORE COMPETENCIES**

- Communication
- Teamwork
- Critical Analysis
- Adaptation
- Organization
- Multi-tasking

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cleanout Pros – Syracuse, New York Citywide Cleanup and Relocation Specialist (8/2024 - present)

Worked closely with a team across the city of Syracuse on a variety of tasks. Managed projects involving demolition, hauling, and thorough cleaning of homes. Assisted clients with moving and relocating their belongings to new residences, ensuring a smooth and efficient process. Created the commercial website for the company.

## Family Caregiver – Liverpool, New York

(4/2023 - present)

Provided comprehensive in-home care for elderly parents, including managing household maintenance, grocery shopping, meal preparation, and cleaning. Ensured the well-being of the family pets through regular walking, feeding and administering medication. Adhered to a structured schedule to maintain consistency and reliability.

# **Belvista Software** – Rochester, New York Intern / Database associate – (11/2022 – 5/2023)

Queried multiple databases in MySQL to search for information helpful to our clients; I provided SSRS reports tailored to clients' needs using this information. In order to appropriately meet the requirements of this position, I consistently prioritized my obligation to clearly understand the specific needs of each client. Responsibilities of position also provided the opportunity to study the use of, and apply my knowledge of, terms specific to the financial/debt industry. I enjoyed this remote work experience while practicing communication skills necessary to successfully work with others in such environments.

# **Skaneateles Country Club** – Skaneateles, New York **Banquet Chef** – (4/2018-12/2019, 6/2022 – 9/2022)

I primarily filled the requirements of Banquet Chef position; that is, I organized time, people and products in a fast-paced environment to feed hundreds of people for each meal. I ordered food, scheduled time of employees, and expedited on the A la Carte lunch and dinner shifts. During weeks our team had no Executive Chef, I filled requirements of that position's responsibilities until replacements could join us. During busy seasons, I often worked several shifts, upwards of 12 hours, for most days of the season.

### **EDUCATION AND TRAINING**

### **EARNED DEGREE'S**

SUNY Oswego, Oswego, New York (8/2021 – 8/2023) - Computer Science B.S. Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, New York (08/2020-5/2021) – Computer Science A.S.

Paul Smith's College, Paul Smiths, New York (08/2015-12/2017) – Culinary Arts and Service Management Onondaga Community College, Syracuse, New York (05/2011, 08/2013) – Hospitality/Restaurant Management

Liverpool High School, Liverpool, New York (05/2009) – High school Diploma

### **Other Skills**

Proficient in Java, C#, HTML, CSS, Python, SQL, Racket, Arduino, Microsoft word, PowerPoint, Excel

Personal Website: https://habshanty.github.io/

GitHub page: <a href="https://github.com/HabShanty?tab=repositories">https://github.com/HabShanty?tab=repositories</a>

3.35 GPA at SUNY Oswego